AGHIN RAJ

India | Bangalore | Aghinraj.raj@gmail.com |

Summa

ry

Driven ABAP Developer with 5.4 years leading technical knowledge to generate IT design, thought and implementation. Resourceful experience researching and crafting custom procedures and processes to resolve technical problems related to SAP. Excels at charting workflow and writing specifications for ideal procedures, knowledge to support IT service delivery and troubleshooting.

Skills

•	Data Dictionary	•	OData
•	ABAP	•	CDS Views
•	OO ABAP	•	AMDP
•	WORFKLOW	•	Enhancements
	Adobe Forms CDS	•	BOPF Fiori elements
•	ABAP Reports	•	Fiori (Basics)

Experience Summary

SAP Associate Technical Consultant

March 2022 - Present / Infosys

SAP Associate Technical Consultant

June 2019 - February 2022 / PEOL Technologies Private Limited

Education

MCA	18	03/2019
BCA 12th Standard	-	04/2016 05/2013
10th Standard		04/2011

Relevant Project Experience

APPLE -	2022 - present
Project Type	Production / S4HANA Implementation
Role	Senior Associate Consultant
Duration	2022 to present
Module	SD , Fi
Tools & Technology	IDocs, RICEFW,ABAP, OOPS ABAP, Data Dictionary, ODATA,, AMDP and CDS Views,RAP,BTP
Responsibilities	 Worked on enhancement for E-invoicing to different countries through IDocs. Working as the lead developer and purposing the solution best suited for the business requirement as well as training the peers. Created some reports for uploading data in format of excels or text file, validations and filtration of data before execution of BAPI. Created smart CDS search help with local binding & additional binding. Created CDS Views with Annotations to integrate as Search Helps in Fiori application. Worked on configuring FI activities, access sequence. Implemented Program exit triggered mail and user decision to external system. Developed CDS Views and consumed it using OData service to achieve aggregation. Worked on report using OO ALV and event Management of ALV, fetching logic, screen designing, attachments using DMS, background job for fetching the records and posting a document using BAPI Implemented BADI, user exists and implicit enhancement for various development. Resolving OData services errors. Worked on performance issues, SCI, ATC, SLIN checks. Writing of well optimized code and doing code reviews for fellow colleagues. Shadowed team on BTP and RAP areas in live projects

WIPRO - Quan	tum	2020 - 2022
Project Type	S4HANA Implementation	
Role	ABAP Technical Consultant	
Duration	01/2020 to 2022	
Module	SD (Sales and Delivery), CPM (Commercial Projec	t Management),Fi
Tools & Technology	ABAP, OOPS ABAP, Data Dictionary, ODATA, Work Views	tflow, BOPF, AMDP and CDS

Responsibilities	 Developed OData services for custom application related to Project
	System, Commercial Project Management, Sales and Distribution to
	perform CRUD Operation.
	 Created custom fiori application using CDS - BOPF fiori elements methods
	 Worked on Roles and authorization, controlled using CDS vies.
	 Created smart CDS search help with local binding & additional binding.
	 Created CDS Views with Annotations to integrate as Search Helps in Fiori
	application using BOPF Fiori Elements.
	Developed configurable Workflows for CPM and FI Modules.
	Implemented Program exit triggered mail and user decision to external
	system.
	Developed CDS Views and consumed it using OData service to
	achieve aggregation.
	Developed Report for data migration using excel upload/download from
	different system.
	 Developed Fiori List Report using CDS Views and annotations.
	 Worked on BOPF using CDS views to achieve CRUD operation and
	created determinations and actions to handle validation and custom
	operations using Fiori Elements.
	Implemented BADI, user exists and implicit enhancement for various
	development.
	Enhanced Fiori application to integrate attachments.
	Resolving bugs related to Workflow and OData services.
	Configured SAP standard application My-Inbox for Workflow.
	Worked in CRM system
	Treated in City of Section

CFMS (Govt. o	of AP) - PHASE 2 4 Months		
Project Type	S4HANA Implementation and Support		
Role	ABAP Technical Consultant		
Tools & Technology	ABAP, OOPS ABAP, Data Dictionary, ODATA, Adobe Forms, AMDP, Workflow.		
Responsibilities	 Developed Various Reports for Background Job Processing. Created OData Entities, Association and Navigation. Created View Cluster for providing user-friendly data maintenance. Created Adobe Forms for various Application. Supported Workflow for Financial Loan Approval and Facility Approval. Worked on Implicit Enhancements for Loan Creation. Supported Fiori Apps for all the custom application. Supported new req for report to Create Purchase Oder using Excel Upload. 		

SAP(Project Alma PHASE1	arai) - 2-Months
Project Type	S4HANA Implementation
Role	ABAP Technical Consultant
Tools & Technology	BADI, ABAP, OOPS ABAP, Data Dictionary, Report, OData
Responsibilities	Worked on Report (PPDS) Display hierarchical ALV for display. Implemented BADI, user exists and implicit enhancement development OData, CURD Operations

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 18 October 1995

• Hobbies: Playing Football.

· Language Known: English, Malayalam, Kannada.

AGENCY EXPIRED CANDIDATE

RAJ, AGHIN

9567516688 aghinraj.raj@gmail.com